BRENTARSENAULT

Boston, MA brent1221@gmail.com (978) 994 9541

Overview

An experienced front-end focused developer who gets excited about the process of bringing work to life for users. Focused on helping projects get to the finish line by pinpointing problems, finding solutions and architecting the technical requirements for an effective result.

Experience

Rightpoint Boston, MA Lead Developer, CMS April 2022 - Present

- Lead deep-dive discussions into technical architecture planning to meet business requirements
- Collaborate with internal team members in a mentor & leader capacity to help drive knowledge throughout the team
- Create and present demoes within sprint cadence to multiple clients
- Partner with multiple disciplines on project kickoffs, planning, builds and approvals
- Pilot front end solutions with internal tool for business development
- Continued excellence in gaining knowledge of emerging technologies

DigitasLBi
Lead Front End Developer
Senior Front End Developer

Boston, MA February 2021 - April 2022 January 2015 - February 2021

- · Led large scale project builds for clients on AEM 6.3, 6.4 platform including multiple frameworks
- Helped create tech solutions with collaboration between multiple departments
- Managed small teams to complete feature and maintain on sprint cadence for releases
- Create component libraries using Vue + Nuxtjs with Nuxt Storybook to deliver for incorporation into client code base
- Responsible for presenting and answering questions during client sprint reviews throughout project lifecycle

AKQA
Senior Creative Developer
Creative Developer

San Francisco, CA July 2014 - January 2015 August 2011 - June 2014

- Led mobile first responsive architecture development standards on usa.visa.com redesign
- Created and maintained documentation for hand off to developers joining team
- Work within a Ruby on Rails environment using BackboneJS & middleman build process to output code to production
- Estimate and create sprint plan tasks for project preparation from a tech standpoint

Beyond Digital Consultancy
Front End Developer

San Francisco, CA January 2011 - August 2011

*Arnold Worldwide Inc.*User Interface Developer

Boston,MA June 2008 - January 2011

Education

The New England Institute of Art, Brookline, MA Bachelor of Science in Interactive Media Design, 2008

Life Interests

Family, Traveling, Sports, Cooking, Lawn & Board Games, Snowboarding, Kayaking/Paddleboarding, Gaming

LEAD FRONT END ENGINEE